I I I please just put your hand on your
head and say I receive understanding I
receive understand because this morning
I want to talk about the ceiling of the
Mind the ceiling of the
mind I I tried yesterday night to
prepare some notes it was quite
impossible um and I knew God wanted me
to speak from his
Dimension and and and this morning when
I woke up the Lord began to reveal
things and and it was a a w moment for
me because sometimes you preach but God
can open one scripture in a way that you
have never
seen when we come to the Book of Genesis
we must appreciate that man is
considered as a Triune being a Triune
being man is Con considered as a Triune
being what do I mean by the word
Triune that means Man exist in three
dimensions man exists in three
dimensions Triune simply means
three and man when we look at the
biblical terminologies and
tenses man exists as a created being a
formed being and a breathed
being Man exist number one as a formed
as a created being man number one exists
as a created being we find this in the
Book of Genesis chapter number one
beginning from verse 6 and then verse I
mean verse 26 and then verse
27 uh Genesis chapter number 1 uh 26 and
then 27 maybe we can check that out out
then God said let us make man in our
image and um according to our likeness
so the word they make the word they make
is God speaking about the totality of
the person that you will be let me
explain it when you come to the word
make the the the essence of that make
produced a creation a formation and a
breathed being so that make is the the
final thing that God wanted to see but
before that man appeared the one that
God wanted to see he had to go through
being created being formed and being
breathed into now we will go slowly
you'll catch up because I know it is in
the morning and you are smart guys so
let us make man in our image according
to our likeness I've said this before
the word there ought to be
mankind the mankind there is a kind God
is saying let us make a kind that is
like us so this is mankind because there
is Mankind and there is the
humankind those are two different
operations the mankind is a kind of God
that is man but the humankind is a kind
that came from humus which is the
soil so so so so now we need to
understand let them have dominion over
the fish of the sea over the birs of the
air and over the cattle and over all the
Earth and every creeping thing that
Creepers on the earth now when you go to
27 God does not make so God created the
initial statement was let us make but
when we come to 27 God
creates this is not a problem of grammar
but this is very intentional when we
come to the objective and what God wants
to achieve at the end of the day now we
begin to see that now God creates a man
and this man is in the god level what is
the word create the name create simply
means bringing into existence out of
nothing that tells me the man that God
created does not have a reference of
consultation because that man was
brought into existence out of
nothing it is the same word we find when
we are talking about the creatives the
word create means to bring into
existence out of nothing so this is the
very word we find when we talk about
creatives like like today the the the
the the song that was done is a song I
have heard but the way it was done it
was done in a way I have never heard it
meaning that someone has brought a
dimension but we don't have a reference
of consultation
it is in existence but it had not
existed
before that is to create meaning that
the first man or this man that God
brings into existence the only way we
can understand that man is by going back
to the one who caused the man to
exist the one that created the man
because God brings him out of nothing
and man appears and this man here this
man here he created him male and female
he created them you can see how that man
exists this man here is a spirit man are
we together are we together now this man
is a spirit man this man is a spirit man
so the created man is a spirit man the
created man is a spirit man we are
looking at the Triune dimension of
man man existing as a
trinity 3 in one so this is a created
man and this man is a
spirit and and the Mystery of this man
is that the assignment of man was not
given when man appeared as a form but
the assignment of man was given when and
man was a
spirit and and that is standard you can
never know your assignment in the flesh
you can only know your assignment when
you locate the original you in the
spirit now we can tie this down with
Jeremiah chapter number one and verse 5
I'm just laying a foundation because my
focus is not on the created man this is
this is for the school of adulam
because part of the lectures in the
school of adulam is who am I in the
spirit and why am I not becoming that
man in the real of the flesh that's a
lecture we need to go through going back
to the original you Hallelujah and that
Dimension carries dimensions of in the
spirit did I carry
diabetes so now we must conform to the
reality of who God created me me the
spirit but for the sake of foundation
let me just lay it here so if you are
new we have a school called the school
of adulam is open for all uh where we
accommodate ordinary men and launch out
Mighty
Men that's the school and and part of
the students who have enrolled their
Captain is a runaway Captain running
from Saul he has an anointing but Saul
is afraid of him that's their captain
and and the students are are
discontented they are in debt
and they are distressed what a class and
and out of those men a mighty warrior
like the army of the Lord will arise
Hallelujah and and you can consult the
previous lectures we opened the school
two Sundays ago so we have not Advanced
for the visitors you can be a scholar
some are borders those are the sons in
the house Hallelujah so the Bible says
before I formed you in the womb so you
see the word there is formed meaning
that there is a formed man but there is
a created man so what is God trying to
tell Elijah I mean Jeremiah that if you
begin to understand you from the
dimension of formation you will never
know who you are because the form real
has biases but there is a real before
you are born I Sanctified you I ordained
you a prophet to the nation so Jeremiah
you need to know yourself in the before
because when you know yourself in the
now you will not make
it so there is a created
man and there is a formed man the
assignment of man let's celebrate my
wife
hallelujah
[Music]
amen and she's not late
I have two children and I can tell you
even me if I was to come if you were to
leave me to take care of them I would
have come here at
lunchtime by the time you change this
one diaper this one has pooped now you
begin the ecosystem of fresh it will
celebrate you Mom are we there because I
want to go slowly are we together
because there there are things here when
you begin to understand them something
will begin to shift in your mind that I
Sanctified you ordained you a prophet to
the Nations so that tells me Jeremiah
did not become a prophet when he
prophesied the Lord is saying
before you appeared in your mother's
womb the ordination in the spirit you
are a prophet so Jeremiah until you sech
yourself in the spirit you don't know
who you are because the one I created
might be limited by the one I have
formed and the assignment is not in the
formation the assignment is in the
creation but the problem is the created
being cannot have access on Earth
without a
form so the only way to access Earth and
do the work of the spirit is to have a
form so what is that form is the body so
the body is the form that has to be now
formed so that it can give the created
man the
opportunity to implement the assignment
of Zion in the real of the earth now the
problem has been many of us we have
never known ourselves in the spirit but
we have known ourselves in the form
remember we said there are three
dimensional of your existence number one
they created you and that's the spirit
man are we together number two we have
the formed you and number three we have
the breathe the one that was breathed
into so you exist as a form as a
creation and as a
breath so we need to understand all this
because somehow they are
interconnected there are two dimensions
of man that is not exploited and those
two diens Dimensions reveal the real
you we don't teach a lot about the soul
and the spirit but there is a lot of
teachings concerning the body the
form now let's go to Genesis chapter
number 2 and verse 7 let's see what God
did because out of this now two things
come into existence two things come into
existence have you understood up to
there that you are a spirit are we
together that's why Paul come and says
we now know no man after the flesh
that's why I am limited when I judge you
by appearance I must shake your hand and
Google you in the spirit to know who you
are and the reality is this time when
the Lord is coming to speak to Jeremiah
the man had not begun assignment but
according to Heaven he was the prophet
of the Nations so there are people who
could be sitting here they have not yet
manifested but in them is the realities
of Eternity that's why never ignore
anyone in any season of life because you
don't know who they are going to be
because ordination is hidden so we can't
relate with you according to the flesh
today you could be in the seasons of
Life today you could be a Ruth who is a
weow k who is a widow who is now
entering into Israel
as a refugee but behind that Widow and
Refugee is the great grandmother of
Jesus because when she steps into
ordination she begins to manifest the
reality of her life so never judge a man
by their current season because you
don't know whom they going to
be some of us we are living testimonies
of what God can do and you too the
moment you begin to discover yourself in
the spirit some barriers will Begin to
Fall that's why I refuse to look at you
casually yes today you could be a house
help but that could be the place of your
entry but that's not the manifestation
of your destiny so never
allow my goodness never allow the
realities of the formed man to limit the
realities of the spirit man because when
the Lord addresses you he doesn't
address you as a form the Lord addresses
you as a spirit Abraham you are the
father of many nations you are it is not
that it's not that you are about to
become an eternal grammar you are a
father Yes but I have a baren wife
listen when I created you I never
created a man without a child is only
that the form according to the grammar
of medicine the form can be called baren
but according to realities of creation
you are a father and the language now is
walk before me and be blameless meaning
that the walk a walk with God is a walk
of knowing god and as I begin to know
God I begin to know me because the one
that created me is the only one who can
reveal me to me K that's why there is a
walk you need to adapt some of you you
have many BFFs can you make Jesus your
bfff because in the Journey of life he
will begin to tell you do you know this
is what you are born limuru that's the
location of your appearance but
according to Destiny and ordination you
are not just another Statistics in
limuru you are a global Shaker so the
mindset of limuru must begin to leave
your
mind that's the problem many of us have
a relationship with the form we have
abandoned the relationship with the
created and even me I can't tell you who
you are and many people are living life
subst standardly
many of us have not even entered to what
God has called us to be never confuse
interaction with Pharaoh as an
endorsement of Destiny because you could
be in the palace but in you is the one
who's meant to confront Pharaoh so
according to God Moses had not begun to
live as long as he was in the opulence
of Pharaoh's house never confuse
material wellness and success is an
affirmation that you're in the path of
Destiny you can be well materially but
when Heaven checks the schedule and the
calendar of your life you are existing
but you have never
lived I know you have a million
followers on Tik Tok I know you are the
inting on Facebook but what is the
utterance of Zion concerning the created
being because the form has become the
pattern of our limitation we can stay
there majority of the sins in church
they are sins of the form it's
flesh that someone can Destiny
because they are
single because the only thing you don't
have is another
[Music]
form that after
form the Bible says and the
Lord God did what
formed of the Dust of the ground found
let's stay there God formed what did God
do so we are coming from God created is
the same person every entity of your
life the flesh never came from the devil
it's only that if you don't understand
the purpose of the form the devil will
show you the other assignment of that
form a lot of our counselings is flesh
and you see that's where that's was the
first Temptation it to subject the form
into some level of appetite and I'll
come to that and that's why man fell in
the first realm of appetite he never
mastered the form because according to
the man God created in the spirit that
man was like
God the Bible says let us make
mankind a kind of us that is man but
this one now will have our image what is
that image this one will have our
projection and our abilities according
to God Adam was like God it's only that
Adam when he appeared in a form he
didn't know who he was in the
spirit so this was not Revelation to God
it was Revelation to Adam the problem
the source of revealing is not Zion you
know the Bible says and the Lord walked
the Bible says and the voice of the Lord
came walking in the
garden the interaction of Eden was not
man meeting a God in terms of physically
it was man encountering a
sound Genesis the Bible says and the
voice of the Lord God Was Heard walking
in the garden meaning that every day the
place of their meeting was not a place
of physical encounter it was man
submitting under sound
because it is sound that will begin to
reveal you to the
form let me go
slowly in Revelation the Bible says and
I Heard a Voice then I turned to check
the source of the voice then I saw Jesus
so that pattern in Revelation was the
same that was meant to be used in
Genesis that man will hear a voice and
once God gets the attention of man now
God will reveal himself to man and I'll
tell you why God could not come directly
to man because you can't understand God
by one encounter it will take eternity
to know God even what we know about God
is what our small minds can
[Music]
grasp and sometimes for God to come in
our level guess what he will do God will
come to our level and use human
terminologies to reveal
himself if Propet there will tell you
they're called
anthropomorphism where God now says I
have hands but he doesn't have a hand I
have eyes the eyes of the Lord are
moving to and fro the ears of the Lord
are attentive God does not have eyes he
doesn't have ears he's a spirit but for
him to help you understand him he must
use features that you have so that you
may begin to Fathom about him but when
Paul the the the custodian of mysteries
when Paul is writing about God he speaks
about the mystery of the
godhead that mystery means it's hidden
it's complex it's technical we we can't
explain him in grammar that's why the
only thing John the Revelation could do
is write in symbolism whatever he saw in
heaven he began to compare with what is
on Earth because whatever he saw there
is no grammar to capture it and put it
into literature it was too deep for man
to handle and that book alone he said
whoever reads not understand understand
he knew is
blessed what he was seeing unless you
see you can't understand it's one of the
most contentious books many theologians
have written from the days of Paul up to
now they are still writing because the
man wrote from a where many of us have
never entered so we can only think from
our so when you hear there's a there's
something coming from the sea you you
are seeing this sea but the man what he
saw is a differ
see oh let's sck you see you see even
way you're looking at
me whatever God has permitted us to know
is a very small portion that's why when
we get raptured do you know what will
happen the Bible says the New Jerusalem
will come down in the new Earth and then
the Throne of Elohim will also be there
and what will it be there will be no
need for sun the Marine Kingdom will be
dealt with the biggest territory of the
enemy so there will be no sea and then
the Throne of Elohim will sit down and
what will happen there will be radiation
of light globally that language of light
is not like as of the sun is radiation
of his
Revelations man will take eternity to
know God that's why every Revelation
projects a man to a posture of
postra when you begin to meet God in the
realm of Revelation you will be like the
24 Elders who cast their crowns and lie
down and say what is the
lamb
okay where are we somebody say I receive
understanding so so now there is a
formed man tell your neighbor there's a
formed man please touch that neighbor
tell that neighbor this is the
form it can be black it can be white it
can be yellow it's not about the color
it's just the
form Hallelujah it can be tall it can be
short nobody cares about your
height you know sometimes when that when
I I love that worshiper my my my son
here when he guess the mic go God go you
know they say up and down that's God you
can't
argue but going this way this is man but
I tell you the truth when he gets the
mic he can make a thousand men shout
it's not about height it's about the God
that you carry and I didn't say you are
short I know you in the spirit you have
very tall you are a Goliad in the spirit
so it's not about the height somebody
say it's not about the
height have you realized many people are
caught up in mood swings oh I don't like
my forehead oh I don't like my nose I
don't like my legs listen nobody cares
about your nose and your forehead when
you begin to know yourself in the spirit
you will discover it's not about the
size of the nose it's not about the
color it's not about the body physique
it's about the anointing and the Mandate
of Elohim upon you
life all these are biases of men that
this is how Beauty looks like this is
how handsome men look like some ear back
being
handsome and some of us we cannot
fulfill
Destiny because even the beers have
refused to gather and assemble they are
not gathering in order tell your
neighbor it's not about the form because
I want to deal with the form before I
even come to the mind because many of us
have permitted the flesh to become our
limitation sometimes I read a book
called get out of your own way the
barrier of the flesh has become
something that has made many people not
to experience the spiritual expression
of who they are sometimes Heaven watches
Humanity on Earth with tears because the
man God created is not the man becoming
because the enemy has perpetually
invested in the form
and and I tell you there is nothing that
people have invested Intelligence on as
the form because everyone knows without
the form I'm not relevant on the earth
that is called the law of rams Spirits
cannot enter Earth without a body so you
need the form to access Earth but that
does not mean the form limits the
operation of the spirit you see I needed
a car to come to church but that does
not mean that the car ought to limit my
worship when I come people always say
meaning that
is that body is privileged to carry you
it's a privilege for that body to carry
you and you need to take care of it
because you don't have another form and
you need to understand that body is Ted
with a few things and you have to govern
them because when the enemy came he
messed up the territory we call the arm
so man must understand how to live with
the form but the greatest Revelation is
the revelation of
creation
now I am born in
samburu and this one I called them the
biases of life and I live in a
community where my father and please
listen to me I'm saying this and you
have to listen well and I love my father
and my parents have been raised in a
community that is biased and the first
bias
is you have to listen spiritually
is without education I'm not going
anywhere and I appreciate education and
they take me through a system and a
channel called school and I go to
primary I go to secondary and I
graduate and the bias of Life tells me
when I'm a graduate and I have a first
class I need to be employed someone must
give me a job and now I am depressed
because someone is not giving me a job
because they began to tune my life to
the biases of life because life was
designed to make me know that when I
move from primary school and my name
appears on the newspaper I need to be in
a national school now I go to the
alliance and out of the alliance I come
out with grades and I go to V Nairobi
University and now there is a perception
of bias that I'm already successful
because I've gone through the bias
system of life and then I ought to wait
for a man to employ me give me a job do
my masters get promotion and as I'm
employed the greatest Li I can enter is
now begin to travel the globe as I
represent my employer and life captures
it as
success and that looks like is the path
of life and everyone has has that bias
in their mind and then after that you be
build a big house in kambu Road buy a
big car and put some little money and
die and now you are faulty you are
depressed because you don't have a big
car you don't have a big house because
the biases of Life have defined these
things as success when you go to the
intention of Academia when you go to the
founders of what we call academic
curriculums and syllabus they were not
there to raise men who are supposed to
conquer the world they were there to
prepare workers for their Mega
companies study Academia beginning from
the 16th century when it was captured
into schools and all that the original
concept of school was where a man that
has mastered a certain art will transfer
knowledge and begin to replicate himself
so that now you don't have one Pastor
who is powerful everyone is a pastor
because you open a place of duplication
and replication and that's why we get
the name disciple not
students because a disciple is a man
trained in the disciplines of the master
that's why after 3 years what Jesus was
doing the disciples were
doing to a point they looked at Peter
and said this man must have been with
Jesus is someone getting me now some
Elites came up in the days of
industrialization and they discovered we
don't have men that can work for us so
what do we do let's begin to introduce
curriculums teach them English teach
them SW it's called communication then
teach them a little bit of History so
that they understand the globe then now
let's begin to Master on economics and
all these things and let's begin to
teach them on
management not to manage their own
and they begin to tune your mind not
ever to be Innovative and creative but
to be in a biased call a man must give
me a
job and I'm not saying there is no place
for employment please get me right but
I'm trying to open up your mind to begin
to break the biases of life and begin to
ask yourself who am I if if I didn't get
born again right now I will be possibly
in nakuru
geothermal employed as a geologist maybe
earning 180,000 that's good money and
because there is free house and all that
that's where I will be and maybe it
would have taken me many years to be
where even I am today but when I began
to know who I was in the spirit I was
not a geologist but there is a system
that can tune my form to begin to
believe that I all I need to be is a
geologist begin to drop the titles the
world gave you and interact with the
spirit and ask the Lord who am I I know
I'm a medical student but who am I I
know I'm an architect but who am I I
know I'm an engineer but Lord before
before who am I because the world can
bind you in some biases and many people
live in areas where nothing no
precipitate of Grace have begun to
manifest and that's why life becomes dep
depressing whatever you are doing is not
exciting and don't get me wrong there
are things we do because we have to feed
our children but those things don't take
80% of our time they only take 20%
because it's a law of work but there are
things we do not because of our children
but because of Eternal
vibrations and I tell you now you go the
media is tuned to produce more
workers right now what is the greatest
cry of genz atuna my job because the
system configured a generation to think
once I graduate a man must employ
me and the system began to introduce
nonsense on Tik Tok that the best thing
you can be is a Dancer there's no
innovation no creation so even those who
are trying to think different they look
like they are mad and imitation becomes
the order of the day and it looks like
in Kenya we can't innovate anything
we'll wait for Nigeria to come up with a
profusion we copy we wait for Tanzania
to come up with Bongo we copy we wait
for India to come up with banga we copy
it looks like there is no Spirit of
innovation and the second thing it looks
like anyone that tries to innovate we
all attack him a man attempted to
innovate at Tuk Tok in like Kia he was
trolled
online because that's the spirit there
is a spirit of killing our own but
celebrating strangers that ceiling must
be broken that ceiling must be broken
this is a land that eat its own it eat
its own but this is the best place for a
man to develop muscles because Champions
are not trained on easy grounds when you
go to those who run in athletics they
don't run in valleys they run in high
places where oxygen is limited because
the altitudes are high and you must
sustain a certain capacity in your
organs to breathe and still learn
because when you exercise in the valley
there is too much
oxygen that's why they go to elor and
not
machakos high altitudes so that your
lungs can develop capacity to keep
oxygen when you are running and hold
your breath so that you can sustain your
peace so there are many ceilings that we
need to break in Kenya I tell you the
truth people have money but no ideas
that's why when someone does something
after one year everyone is doing it
it you just come up with an idea
everyone is doing what does that tell
you we don't have room for Innovation
meaning that the biases of the form have
become our order you open a business and
it succeeds then you hear there are
thousand and guess what is the pattern
of marketing attacking each
other someone wrote a book called The
Ocean the blue ocean he was say the
ocean is so big that all a will needs to
do is discover a new
territory sometimes I drive through
suswa I see vast lands open and be but
we are all fighting to live in
Nairobi do you know the colonialist when
they discovered Nairobi it was a be
land the concept of Nairobi it began as
a railway station it was not meant to be
a city the city was meant to be in
kikuyu because the British preferred
living in areas that represent their
weather but because of the of the
Railway Station they they they they now
lived there and now the city came up
many of the cities were abandoned areas
that tells me you can carry a Grace and
Pioneer City in a desert we don't need
to fight for land where everyone is
fighting for land you can just go in a
state and God has given us that Grace we
always go in places where there is
nothing and it is part of the Dominion
mandate part of the Dominion mandate is
called subdue subdue is to bring
functionality that which is not
functional that is
subdue contain after
space and you pioner something on the
other side and guys are like how did you
see this is because I know who I am in
the
spirit know who I am in the spirit is
someone getting me one of the personal
Walks With God is for the Lord to begin
to tell us who we are who we are if if I
was to grow with the bias of my Village
because even Villages have
biases if I was to be limited by the
understanding of my parents I will not
be where I am somebody say
biases Hallelujah we can't dwell there
because we can make all prayers and
anoint you but when the ceiling of the
mind is not broken you can't go
far the first thing that has to be dealt
with is the mind and and what happens is
that when the form is subjected in an
environment of biases maintain to
conform to that
environment can I surprise you in South
Africa pros and
TXS are not car considered to be car for
the wealthy in fact they say anytime you
see a PR a TX and a har that car must be
going somewhere in Kenya or East Africa
and do you know who gives value to cars
in Kenya
presidents whatever the king drives
let's celebrate Minister
Harriet and the team that is
coming can I give you
intelligence yes whatever the president
arrives in Kenya is considered as the
laxaria SK of the day
in the days of the late
kibaki in the days of Moy
pajeros by the order of the day any man
with a pagero was a rich man because the
king is driving a pagero then uh the Le
Kaki took power his favorite car was a
Benz those days any man with a Mercedes
was rich then uh uh the former president
huru introduced
passats and somewhere people began to
look at the Volkswagen and now in the
age again of uru the pr was kicked in
now our current president is in
Lexus now today and he J alland your
husband
[Music]
welcome the former president was seen
driving a G wagon and then um right now
now it's either you have a gagon a Range
Rover or a Lexus now when you go to
Dubai Pros are used for Desert Safari
[Music]
but when a man comes with a PR in Kenya
What rings in your mind
wealth when you go in
Europe they consider driving a small car
is more reasonable because of foel and
because of parking you you look human
when you have a
bitter but in
Kenya the wife must have a Gaza the
husband must have a Gaza in the
security and
shades these are the biases we are
talking about am I speaking to anyone
and and when you travel the globe you
begin to realize every territory has
certain defined biases and and you can't
outli them until you begin to know who
am I in the spirit who sets my standards
who is the one that has drawn the
boundaries of my
life a friend of mine was making a joke
and he was
saying some of the people Jimmy Western
Kenya their vision is to have a
[Music]
por please ask ask that neighbor who is
responsible possible for the barriers
and the ceilings of your
life what is that that you consider and
say this is now success who defined that
who made you come to a point and say
this is now
success is it what you have seen or
heard or is it what the Holy Spirit has
permitted you to
see men like Abraham died looking for a
city whose Builder is God
that's why there are people
pride is a product of resting
early when you reach a place and think
this is all life can
offer the next thing that you are going
to conceive is pride because someone
made you believe if you drive what the
president is driving you have made it if
you live where the CSS are living you
have made it if you shop where the
governors are shopping you have made it
who defines the ceilings of your life is
it the buyers of society or is it the
standards of
scripture I was watching Bishop David
Oedo launch his
church
100,000 C Church debt free he said all
the money is in the bank he was
launching so that the building can
begin now he here we launch so that
people can give there the money is in
the bank they have given now they are
commissioning the project to continue
and he said God never called us to build
churches he called us to build cities I
switched off the TV I didn't want to
hear the next statement because I was in
a church project because where I live in
my territory the buyers and the ceiling
is a church ma Kua now sound KUB Now
parking in a j but there are men who
have moved from structures that the
church is not what is inspiring them to
build they are Builders of cities and
the church is part of it I said
Lord but
here that's why we must not we must stop
looking at men and look at God because
if men set our standards we will retire
early but when God is the one setting
your standard you will not rest because
of premature celebrations some of you
you rested because now you are the
village Champion get in the city
interact with men you'll discover you
are a small
boy there's what we call premature
celebration men look at you and they
think you've made it because according
to their level you're above but who sets
the level that's what I want you to ask
yourself this morning who set the
ceilings that you're operating on who
set the tets is it men or is it the Holy
Spirit are you growing according to
ordination or are you growing according
to
[Music]
competition and now we come now to the
man that God breathed look at the same
scripture Genesis 2:7 this one will
continue in the school of adulam we
can't finish today
Hallelujah go back to the Bible says and
God formed man of the Dust
please tell your neighbor neighbor from
today don't allow the form to limit the
possibilities of the
[Music]
spirit and then the Bible says after God
formed the man what did he do he
breathed into his nostril the breath of
life and
Man
became a living being some version call
it a living soul
so so there is a man there is that's why
we call it the soulish that's the soul
that Soul appeared as the breath that
name breath is roak is the same word
that is used for the Spirit Wind and
also the Breath of God so the
Lord of a
man and that breath was not just wind
when you look at how the bones were
gathered in ezek
the Bible says the winds coordinated the
work of God coordinated to bring the
form and the Soul into existence because
Spirits don't
die that Ezekiel was replicating
Genesis he needed the
work to bring that man to functionality
so what did the Lord do he
breathed and M
became so there was the created
man then there was the formed man after
the breath there was a
becoming he now became a living
[Music]
soul and that name
Soul the Hebrew word is nepes or
nepes that name Soul the Hebrew word is
NEP I'll give you to you because now we
jumping into deeper
waters the name Soul
there is
NEP or nepes neesh and e p h e s h NE e
p h
e s h neesh that's the pronunciation it
means Soul one it it means self
too it means Soul it means self it means
life it means
creature it means
person it means Soul self life creature
person it also means
appetite
appetite it also means
mind it means
desire
desire it means
emotion emotion it means
passion neesh it means Soul self life
creature person appetite mind
desire emotion passion and the final
thing it means living being so this was
a form but it had to be something that
is a living
reality Jesus help me so that tells me
until until we understand the
soul we will never understand self
will never understand the person because
remember you are not the
form you are not the form you are not a
kikuu you are not AA you are not a jaluo
you are not an American you are a spirit
that is housed in a
form and the Soul begins now to give you
identity of who you
are the self the appetites they in the
they in the
soul the desires are in the soul the
emotions are in the soul the passions
are in the
[Music]
soul Let Let me Give an example that
you'll all maybe understand when you buy
a
phone it comes as an object and a gadget
in that
phone it has Google
Facebook it has a play store where you
can download some things and update them
but there are features that come with a
phone when you put the
phone in
charger you can see everything that it
carries are we together but there's
something that has to be inserted for
you to begin to enjoy whatever is there
when you put the SIM
card and then you enter into a data or a
WiFi sensitive area some things will
begin to pop up and they come into
functionality they were already in
existence but there was something that
was not there so when that thing is
introduced now you can enjoy the phone
now the man the man looks like this
phone loaded with with everything that
came from the spirit but there the soul
came to
activate everything that was in
you I'll go further that's why when we
come to the reality of death it is the
soul that leaves the body and when the
soul exists automatically you don't
exist
[Music]
the only man who attempted to teach this
thing was
Solomon the only man who did the
research of death was Solomon and he
discovered there something called the
silver
cord and that silver cord is what
connects the soul with the body the soul
is so much intertwined with the spirit
to a point that when the soul leaves the
spirit of course cannot pick any signals
it leaves and then now you are left with
a body that has eyes knows all these
things but none of the things is
functional because whatever gives
functionality to those things is the
soul the passions the desires the
appetites is the soul that's why when
when you have men that have souls they
have desires and appetites now what the
devil does he canot tune the desires to
be
ungodly he can adjust the appetites to
be desires and appetites of things that
don't
matter oh my
God and I know how you always tell
people me I know myself now this is I'm
talking about
you now do you know what I'm talking
about is something you have and you
don't
know you you know yourself in the
flesh that's a product of the Soul
and that's why it defines self and
that's why there must be an ecosystem to
master it and deal with it now okay let
me break it down so that in a way we can
understand then we end the session but
are you learning something there is a
created
man there is a formed man and there is a
breathed man a man that God breathed
into the soul the soul the soul has put
this down the soul has the conscience
subconscious and memory that is in the
soul it has the conscious subconscious
and
memory the soul the soul
has seat of
emotions seat of
emotions the Gate of
Will and the faculty of
logic it has the seat of emotions the
soul the seat of emotions
the Gate of will decisions actions come
from that gate and faculty of logic
that's the
soul that's the soul and the that thing
that the soul has the soul
houses the five
senses the soul houses the five
senses smell touch hear see and taste
it has the five senses that's why we
always talk about the sensory real it
has the the place of smelling the place
of touching the place of seeing the
place of hearing and the place of
testing all these are constituents of
the
Soul that's why we can't talk about self
if we don't deal with the soul I feel
even like going further how many have
ever gone for soul
winning what were you winning
you see how radical we are Pastor pray
for us we are going for soul winning we
have won five Souls how did do you win
the
souls and did you know that some of
those people you are
winning you had to deal with something
in their memory for them to get your
attention you had to deal with something
in their subconscious they were abused
and those pictures are still there
that's why we
can't we you can't change a man until
you master the
[Music]
soul the whole concept of depression is
an attack of the
Soul because that's where we have the
mind I may not go to I'm not a I'm not a
counselor and all that but I can speak
from where I come from but I know when
we come to the to the the chemicals that
are released in the mind the dop all
these things that are responsible for
addictions you'll begin to discover that
when a man is trained to master his soul
is also trained to master those
chemicals there is a place of counseling
where people are taught disciplines but
there is a place of light where people
receive
impartations some of the most successful
rehabs are the ones that have Christian
schedules on
them I know people who left rehabs and
they teach people how their mind works
because they were taken through
psychological lectures of this is how
addictions works but they didn't
understand there is a superior power
that can make the soul to be submitted
under the power of the
spirit Hallelujah and so so now we are
dealing with a man this man has memory
as conscious subconscious this man has
the faculty of logic as I'm speaking I'm
depositing data in the faculty of logic
and it is that data what you know that
begins to affect what you feel and when
when what you know and what you feel is
affected then what you do is
automatically
affected actions are a product of
intelligence there is no way Eve would
have eaten the fruit if there was no
intelligence it is what she had and knew
that provoked her emotions and her
actions that's why oh my God I shared
somewhere and I said we are living in
Genesis 3 because we are in the age of
information Tik Tok Facebook Twitter one
of the reasons why there is so much
depression globally is because people
know things they have no power to deal
with there is a structure to handle
information there is even a formula to
relay information I see rev here anytime
you go to the hospital hospital and
someone has
died they know how to pass that
information one day we went to see a
doctor and I felt like the doctor was
quite brutal he was reading the results
he said
ah you know he's talking about your life
because there is how we ought to relay
some information and I know men we don't
know how to relay information
especially is this guy
still men we need to change we need to
master the soul that's why you find them
crying after the barrier because even
that bar was not a reality it's after
that reality things and say by this guy
is not there this guy has
left tell your neighbor the soul because
that's where we have the mind are you
getting me that's where we have the mind
and and and what I discovered according
to Romans chapter number 12 this became
my anchor scripture on those beginning
Ministry the Bible says I beseech you
therefore Brethren by the mercies of God
to offer you a body a Living Sacrifice
holy acceptable to God and then he says
now uh which is your reasonable
sacrifice then he goes and says and do
not be conformed what does that mean
whatever I spoke about the biases of
Life the patterns of Life anyone that is
born in life automatically we are born
into a certain bias will conform
naturally it will affect how we think
how we view life how we talk how we
behave now Paul is saying do not be
conformed to this world that name World
there that name World there is systems
and patterns
it's not the physical world but then he
goes and says but be transformed the
word there is
metamorphosed the same way a butterfly
moves from butterfly p lav and become a
butterfly it is a stage transitional
process and there are different
investment put in certain stages so he
was saying for the only way for a man to
enter into new realities is that there
must be a transformation is not
instant and then it says by the renewing
by the renewing some Say by getting a
better mindset of your mind now this
this now this one changes everything it
begins to tell me as a preacher my
theology is useless if I've not
interacted with
psychology because
transformation comes when I have
mastered the mind because if I am able
to change the mind I will be able to
change the
life that's why there are preachings
that go above men's head and they never
change that's why there must be a
marriage between Theology and psychology
because we are trying to bring men from
the kingdom of darkness there is a
psychological pattern and deposit that
made them behave the way they are
behaving so that we bring out them to
the kingdom of light and there is a way
we must begin to pull these matters in
their lives and then he say so that you
may prove what is that good acceptable
and perfect will dimensions of the will
of God it's possible for a man to do
business in the good level it's possible
for a man to do business in the
acceptable level ask Abraham he has
ishma but that's not the perfect that's
the acceptable the day he's taking Hagi
to the tent God had power to release
Thunder and cause floods to carry the
tent and postpone the date but maybe
that day even the moon was so good the
atmosphere was good for the man to
implement
[Music]
acceptable now you can see the most the
powerful
one God brings the best out of you the
the the most mature one is the perfect
will Isaac there are many Christians
working in the acceptable will cuz they
never went to pray they went to disturb
God and God said okay get it or is a
husband you want this one or the one I I
want to give you welcome Pastor
Patrick because you know you can go to
God with your prayer item and you can go
to God to ask him what is his item of
prayer you can bring a man to God but
God can also bring a man to
you and you can come and tell the Lord
father thank you this is the man you've
given me and he's like
who saying father thank you oh this is
amazing but God can also bring a man to
you and God can watch you bring a man
and say it's okay you've insisted and
then you get married later to discover
this was his acceptable it's called
permissive some of us who are very
stubborn at home we know that
language mom is making chapaties and you
begin to
cry because you're the last born and you
cause a f and to make you keep quiet mom
will take one hot chapati one uncooked
potato and give you and then you eat and
your stomach
blots and then when the food is ready
and everyone is enjoying you can't enjoy
because already you are under permissive
will but patient men are now enjoying
perfect
whe School of adulam will deal with this
matter Hallelujah
now listen so I discovered that until
the mind is
mastered there are things we can't do
and I have seven points I want to give
you because my intention for this
session is to release the spirit of
creativity and breaking the ceilings of
mind some of you you must move from
seeking employment to becoming the
employers some of you must move from
that sicker mindset to begin to ask
yourself what can I do with my head some
solutions are not in an office in
fact when they say think out of the box
many offices are
square and I was studying because I read
many things I read many things I I was
reading somewhere and they were saying
anytime you see a cell is a
cube anytime you see a jail is a cube an
office is a cube a class is a cube
meaning that we must break this Cube and
come to a place of cylinders where there
is ideas can flow and go
around and the man was saying there is a
reason why the world is not a cube
because cubes cage men but cylinders
release men to manifest their potentials
I even thought our grandmothers were
wise building round
houses today you move from one Cube
sitting room to another Cube
bedroom you know those round houses they
were self-contained the kitchen is here
the bed is here
so okay let's take so what I discover
the mind the mind we'll build up on this
the the mind is a very amazing thing and
one of the things we need to deal with
is not the prophecies Upon Our Lives is
the barriers that in our minds let me do
a
practicals there is a land there is a
property being sold in
tisi four bedroom
house master and suit on compound the
VIS Nairobi 50
million the there's another property in
tisi it's a two-bedroom house a small
own compound you can still view Nairobi
but it is 25 million you are here you
are single don't have a family there's a
four bedroom there's a two- bedroom
which one will you buy how many will go
for the two-bedroom 25 million it has
the same thing you'll still see Nairobi
and all that the other one is four
bedroom you'll still see Nairobi and all
that how many will go for the one in 25
million please it's it's not a hard
question very don't
lift up your hand lift up your hand how
many will go for the 50 million lift up
your hand how many are still weighing
options lift up your
hands now you see let me show you most
of us when we go there we will go for
the 25
million because number one we have been
cultured with a cheap
mentality number two is not that you
have the 50 and you don't even have the
in both cases you don't have the money
but there is a mindset that tells you
let me go this one I can afford or this
one is cheaper and he giving me the same
privileges I can still
see there is an option to use sgr an
option to fly an option to drive you see
whatever will determine your are means
of transportation sometimes is not money
is mindset
the the VIPs grr is
12,000 4 hours VIP the same money is
what you need for an airplane two and
fr and then there is sgr Kaa you sit
with a man from
bua
Mombasa okay a man from morang
e okay what travel but there is
something in your mind that has
perpetually told you chap is my
level and that's why the vibration for
the next
level has never come let me share what
Minister har told me I've never
forgotten this story so the Lord blesses
them and lifes them and helps them to
have a house in
runda but they have lived in kyol all
their lives and Minister Harriet every
weekend she has to take her clothes to
Don home
lry because it's
cheap moving from
runda to Don
home for close to be washed re thank you
gave me that story for clothes to be
washed and then move from Don Ho and go
to Runa and one day she met someone and
the man never talked to her the man
talked to the HBY and said you know what
your wife is in runda physically but her
mind has never moved to runda how many
people know K you can have prophecies
but your mind has never envisioned
yourself like the man the Lord wants you
to be and that's why the next barrier is
a personal barrier you must break the
ceiling of your mind and tell the Lord
let me think like you let me see like
you it's not about my community yes they
call Kenya a third world country that is
the bias of Economics yes they may call
this area Runa this area ghetto that is
the bias of economy what is in your
[Music]
mind I I was investing in a business and
a man came and told me I love what
you're doing we need to write a proposal
and raise between $10 million to $25
million and then I calculated I realized
that's 1.3 billion to almost uh 3
billion I smiled I said Lord the same
mind that can speak of a million can
also speak of a billion why because I
just need to tune my mind to
billions you see the way you're looking
at me funny I'm Prosperity preacher
[Music]
listen this thing called the mind we
must break it we must break it some of
us that's our bias I have a friend of
mine and is's and I love him so much
guess what the father used to do the
father never came from a privileged
family but the father made networks with
privileged people so every Christmas he
made sure the sons interacted with the
rich Community to begin to open their
mind and tell them where we are this is
not all about life and guess what it
began to instar some vibration that
there is more to life and then the
father will tell him now you see that's
why you need to work hard these things
are possible but you have to work hard
such a man you would find him smoking
now you raise your your your boy karang
goes to karang never expose him and that
boy looks at life and think this is all
life is all about
[Music]
you see that's that's what the community
might have said but you could be raising
a ceiling breaker begin to expose the
child that's why some of us who are not
born in privilege when we get the
opportunity let our children not adapt
our
[Music]
mind one day a woman I
love we decided to buy her
gas and I tell you the truth she used to
use the G in
emergency because there was the mindset
of
Cho one day we sat down we did
calculation we said how much is Cho we
realized gas was cheaper than Cho but
because there is an ancient mindset that
has refused to go something still was
telling her Cho is cheap in in some
years it was cheap but now it is cheap
it is clean and it is affordable but she
could not
see
mindset
bedroom
mindset okay let me let
me oh Hallelujah do you still love me
because I I guess Pastor Ron our problem
is not prophecy our problem is not
anointings sometimes I get tired when I
see how we vibrate in prayer and I'm
saying Lord there must be results in our
lives but I've realized some people have
refused to change their
mindset in and God cannot do it for you
that's why one of the things you need to
begin to read is the Bible because this
is another light this thing will enter
into every fiber of your mind and begin
to make you see the world differently
your lenses about life will change how
you talk how you behave how you confess
it will begin to change because I
discovered anytime you know God does not
speak from a real of of barriers this is
what the Bible says that that With God
all things it doesn't give limitation
all things so when you come from the
real of Elohim you have entered the real
of all things if anything can be called
all God looks at it from All Is An Open
check God is able to do excitingly above
what you can think or even imagine you
know thinking is one thing imagining is
another thinking can be addressed by
imaginations can be strange but God is
still saying he's able to do excitingly
above what you can think or even imagine
then he says and that power is not in
heaven according to the power that is
resident in you because the day you
receive the Holy Ghost you received an
anointing of impossibility I can do all
things through Christ it doesn't say
Jesus because there is Jesus the man but
when he was anointed and baptized the
Holy Ghost came upon him he became Jesus
the Christ so the Christ that's the
anointing that's the Holy Ghost I can do
all things through what the anointing
the power of the Holy Ghost through the
anointing I can do not some when we are
dealing with God he's not coming from a
real of barriers he's coming from a
realm of all possibilities that tells me
I need to open my mind and begin to
embrace God as God begin to embrace him
from his real tell him open my eyes let
me see what you are seeing this
premature celebration should not make me
settle whatever I have achieved is
theary in the calendar of Zion because
we have a God of all possibilities all
possibilities whatever is in your mind
sometimes is your own creation let the
devil not speak to you that's why when
we pray in tongues we are not proving to
our neighbors we are intercessors when
we pray in tongues is not a confirm We
Are Spiritual we are activating the
crystals that anointing that is in you
so that it can begin to move in your
mind and release the light of the Living
God we don't pray in tongues to confirm
we are Pentecostals it is an activator
of the anointing and sometimes as you
pray you begin to see patterns you begin
to see systems you begin to see
structures because some things are in
the god Dimension only God can give
Moses a certain pattern to build a
certain Temple so there are things that
have not yet been done because a man has
not yet attempted can I show you
something in the same scripture Genesis
chapter number 2 and verse 5 this is
what the Bible says it had not rained
because God had not caused it to rain
because there was no man before any
plant of the field was in the earth you
are seeing before and before any h of
the field had grown why for the Lord God
had not caused it to rain on the earth
you can see those things no plants
nothing was there no Hub and no rain
because these things can only manifest
if something happens and the Bible says
and there was no man meaning that as
long as there was no man no h no tree
nothing could have appeared meaning that
there are things that cannot appear
until you appear there are companies
that cannot appear until someone decides
enough is enough I must appear
there are possibilities of Eternity that
can never appear how could Life Church
appear behind someone had to appear for
the city to appear may you begin to
appear in the name of Jesus let the body
of your mind be taken out let the
barriers of your village be taken out
you are a global son your father is not
a villager your father is the creator of
the heavens and the Earth your father is
not bound by the politics of Kenya your
father controls the politics of the
Globe May the Lord plant you where you
are appearing will provoke other things
to appear there is an appearing
Hallelujah that's why you must cut off
The Whispers of men and begin to say I
think I know who I am in the spirit I
know what this body carries I know who I
am this is not the r because now people
are dating older men so that they can
drive Pros in the realm of the spirit
maybe you are supposed to own a showroom
but in the form real you are here bound
because of the appetite of the earth
someone must begin to know who am I in
the spirit why is it that I get
attracted to these things they did a
research in jail and they discovered
every Thief who was C stealing was
manifesting of a dimension that was in
them a dimension of wealth is only that
they were not patient to be trained to
become so they have a genuine Grace for
money
the problem is that they couldn't wait
for the process of Attraction so they
began to manifest in ways that God did
not ordain when you enter committee and
find people who are bank robbers when
you listen to them you'll discover there
was a genuine Grace of wealth but the
process was
abandoned so some of you that thing that
makes you want to date a mama is a
genuine Grace of wealth but there's a
process so live the har women alone
leave the proud on subar boys alone tell
the Lord teach me that process oh Lord
because anyone that has entered the
destination there is a path they have
pursued the appetite is genuine the
process is
wrong and sometimes when he stops being
an idol you'll have it please sit down
let me give you seven
[Music]
things seven things that will give you a
creative
mind creative mind because your are
competition we we we are moving from a
place of competing from a level of
investment to a place of creativity that
is divine number
one these are atmospheres for creativity
number one creativity is Purity
conscious I'll go very quickly
creativity is Purity conscious Holiness
is a factor that delivers our mind from
junk
many men that pioneered Great Things
They Carried a dimension of
consecration you look at a man like
Daniel the King slept and forgot his
dream but the man because of Holiness
not defiling himself he was able to
journey and came up with a dream not
only that he was one of the most
competent Governors that three
governments could not fire him there's a
real of competence the Bible says later
they discovered there was a spirit
called the spirit of Excellence that
could only have been attracted by a
system of Purity you look at a man like
Joseph giving a proposal to deliver the
nation in a time where the nation is
about to enter into abundance and a
season of loss come up with a concept of
banking models you save in scarcity use
in abundance you you save in abundance
use in scarcity and the Bible calls
whatever he gave a proposal but it came
from a pure mind he came from jail a
place of seclusion but he also came from
portier a place of
purity
defilement of the Mind corrupts
creativity you remember the days of
virus you have a very functional machine
but the virus corrupts the
functionality of your machine meaning
that the machine is okay but there is a
virus that is attacking every file sin
sin is a virus that begins to compromise
begins to compromise the power of a
creativity and I'm also coming from a
school of thought that the devil is now
after our minds he left our bodies long
time that's why we are talking of
depression because a depressed mind can
never be creative it is like a it's it's
like a mind that is you know many things
come and and I acknowledge there are
things there are factors that begin to
attack us but when we know our
assignment in the spirit and we know
that opposition will come we already
anticipate it
so we begin to build the muscles of our
minds for what might be coming so number
one somebody say Purity somebody say
Purity I always say your mind your mind
is like a flash dis you have a 64 GB
capacity but 28 GB is bongo
music 10 GB are
frema and then the only GB left is 2 GB
for creativity by the time you think you
will think Nigerian
adverts tell your neighbor guard your
mind someone says something very
powerful the mind is like your body you
can exercise it and the only thing that
the Mind lifts is the weight of
knowledge that's why we need to lift our
minds with books yesterday I sat with
Pastor Gasher and I discovered I found
my tribemate he told me I have a printer
in my room anytime I I see something he
gave me a word I've never gotten he told
me there's something we call Knowledge
harvesting from Google I said
wow this you can Harvest knowledge any
man that is a leader will be a leader in
whatever he does because whatever is
lacking in the globe is the capacity to
read so number one number one please
Purity number two your mind creativity
operates in an atmosphere of
joy that that we call it praise
creativity of operates in an atmosphere
of
Joy some of the most creative men was
was Solomon and David creativity
operates in an atmosphere of Joy Doom
can never give you um you know you can
never think right when you are
perpetually doomed creativity operates
in atmosphere of Praise or
Joy those who frown their faces freeze
their
[Music]
hearts Joy is the mental
ventilation to the
mind if you do not deal with pressure it
becomes tension which matures to be
hypertension that's why they say
laughter is the medicine of the heart
don't just wash
tahola and 1,000 ways to die once in a
while listen to churching ERI laugh
they're not making any sense but just
laugh but not all your life after
Laughing Now focus on life so that you
don't become a laughter I heard a man
say life does not respond to how
handsome you are but life responds to
how your hands can hold
some beard
[Music]
gun manity and you can't hold some but
your
handome Jesus let's
[Music]
continue number three
Enthusiast life responds to
enthusiasm or
creativity that means looking forward
from within
enthusiasm enthusiasm write it in your
mother tongue the notes are
yours the way you read are not this is
enthusiasm this is the joy within that's
why there must be Joy
[Music]
within and I tell you the truth the only
way this thing is activated is when you
begin to build and appreciate the baby
steps now you see we have a whole plan
for this 4.5 acreage of land and the
budgets are crazy so yesterday I decided
to walk to the washrooms that's the only
project that looks complete the fence is
not so if I walk through other areas
I'll be discouraged so yesterday I
walked in the washrooms and you I wish
you could hear me saying now after this
we now go here that that's a 40 million
project we now go here that one we give
ourselves two two months then after that
we go there then we put the foundation
of the church then we do the parking
Cabos 2 Aces around 6 million because
now because one small achievement
ignites Joy that's why you must
celebrate baby steps even though you
have a big
[Music]
picture number four this is the secret
of creativity quietness and
privacy quietness and privacy successful
people are hardly public
people what you do in private announces
you in
public and you're are not doing it in
private to be announced is
automatic any man that labors in private
results will shout for
him majority of the people taking photos
in expensive
hotels they are excited because that's a
place they don't go
frequently wherever you frequent you are
not excited
about people who take photos with
expensive cars they're excited because
that's something they don't frequently
enjoy is not a privilege I've never seen
the president on a selfie stick saying
now here I'm going to Germany guys you
know the man flies almost every week
maybe he's even tired to hear there's
another trip but but you better see a
villager going to out of the country for
the first time you won't breathe from
the reception to the staircases of the
airplane going about in public going
about in public does not make you a
public figure sometimes you may be a
public
nuisance bright ideas come from quiet
places and quiet
Seasons you see Daniel withdrew after
the threat of nebuchad
he said give me time because that's the
only way I can hear him we need times of
withdrawing Jesus had the culture of
withdrawing and staying by himself
number five association with
thinkers association with
thinkers these are the ingredients that
trigger creative minds the one on the
watch you'll know how to do it
association with
thinkers thinkers are ideas
fertilizers when you sit with thinkers
they fatalize your ideas don't sit with
mockers
criticizers Idol men have all the time
to talk about Idol
things you can't be discussing the value
of
Ronaldo yet you don't even know the
identity of your life it's a
chaos thinkers
iron sharpens
iron and sometimes you need people who
can make your ideas look foolish so that
you can think a blind man in the company
of BL I mean a a man with one eye in the
company of blind people is a king but
that man in the company of people who
have two eyes is a
choose your audience wisely some
of you you are Kings but in some faces
you are cripples
this one may look foolish but I've
discovered physical fitness is very good
rest rest I've tried this thing and I
discovered there's reason why God said
you need to rest once one day a week
I've I've seen that pattern and is
therapeutical anytime I rest I'm
productive for 6 days anytime I don't
rest I can only work for 1 hour and
waste 23
hours sometimes one day rest is enough
to acquire your 10 hours for the next 6
six days even Jesus slept who are
you Hallelujah physical
fitness sometimes you need to go to the
gym there's a lot of tension released in
the gym run joke skip a
rope because the mind the Mind loves a
lot of Engagement and you're one
ecosystem father we thank
you just lift up your hand I want to
make a prayer of
faith I am believing God out of this
meeting will see men that have conquered
the barri of the mind will begin to see
creativity that has never been seen in
the atmosphere in this realm I release
you now to Supernatural Minds let this
mind that was in Christ Jesus be in you
let the barrier of the Mind be lifted in
the mighty name of Jesus and and I
announc from DOA by the time we meet
next year DOA we will dedicate companies
products Concepts Solutions Industries
proposals because the anointing is now
running in your mind every barrier that
has limited and hindered you slow
self-esteem you think nobody can do it
we bring it out and we declare you are
one of a kind go and manifest because
the Hall of Heaven is Waiting for your
showing forth let no man stand on your
path we declare that ceiling is
perpetually broken in Jesus name and
somebody say and somebody say Amen
please stand to that neighbor tell that
neighbor from
today my thinking has
shifted and my ceilings of the Mind have
been
broken in the name of Jesus Pastor Ken
Patrick I know I've gone beyond my time
but it's because do happens once in a
year so you can come and give us
Direction God bless you